Are you looking to learn what microservices are?
Or are you trying to get started and gain some real world hands on experience with.
Net microservices.
If yes, then you are at the right course.
My name is Brogan and welcome to the course.
Net Core Microservices.
The Complete Guide.
Microservices is one of the buzzword in programming.
If you look for a new job, microservices is one of the key features that is coming up more and more
often.
Every time a system is lagging or it is getting too big, someone will have a suggestion that maybe
we should look into microservices.
But it is critical to understand what exactly it is and how to implement it correctly.
That is my motivation behind this course.
My goal is to introduce you to the microservices architecture while giving you a real world project
to see how microservices communicate with each other and what are the problems that we encounter and
how to solve them.
Microservices is made up of individual projects in simple terms, but in reality there is much more
to microservices than that.
But as microservices are composed of individual APIs, we will be spending quite some time in building
small APIs.
And then we will focus on the key concept of how individual API communicates with each other and how
the microservices architecture comes together.
We will be building seven small API's in this course, including one API that will be responsible for
authentication and we will do that using Dotnet identity.
Once we build the APIs, then we will see how API communicates with each other.
One of the most frustrating thing when you are learning something is when the course is outdated, because
of which I will always try to keep the content up to date.
That way you will not be struggling with what is different in the new version.
If you are excited about what microservices are and you want to learn by building a real world project
in microservices, this is the course you are looking for.
I hope you will join me in this exciting journey of microservices.
And let me show you what we will build in this course in the next video.